(Music) Open your heart to the incredible gifts that civilization gives to us. You flip a switch, and there is electric light. You turn a faucet, and there is warm water and cold water, and drinkable water. It's a gift that millions and millions in the world will never experience. So these are just a few of an enormous number of gifts to which we can open your heart. And so I wish you that you will open your heart to all these blessings, and let them flow through you, that everyone whom you will meet on this day will be blessed by you, just by your eyes, by your smile, by your touch, just by your presence. Let the gratefulness overflow into blessing all around you. (Music) And then, it will really be a good day. (Applause) Louie Schwartzberg: Thank you. Thank you very much. (Applause)
(Musique) Ouvrez votre cœur aux cadeaux incroyables que la civilisation nous offre. Vous appuyez sur un interrupteur et il y a de la lumière électrique. Vous ouvrez un robinet et il y a de l'eau chaude et de l'eau froide, et de l'eau potable. C'est un cadeau que des millions de gens dans le monde ne connaîtront jamais. Ce ne sont que quelques-uns des innombrables cadeaux auxquels nous pouvons ouvrir nos cœurs. Je vous souhaite donc d'ouvrir votre cœur à toutes ces bénédictions, et de les laisser couler à travers vous. Et tous ceux que vous rencontrerez aujourd'hui seront bénis par vous, rien que par vos yeux, par votre sourire, par votre toucher, rien que par votre présence. Laissez la reconnaissance déborder dans une bénédiction tout autour de vous. Alors, ce sera vraiment une bonne journée. » (Musique) (Applaudissements) Louie Schwartzberg : Merci. Merci beaucoup. (Applaudissements)